http://www.afripics.com/c/privacy-policy

Login
Forgot username or password?
Need help? Contact us
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last updated 23 July 2015
This Website is intended for adults.  If you are under the age of 18 you must not use this website or enter any personal information on any of the interactive areas on the website.
By using this website, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to the terms of this policy.
AfriPics respects your right to privacy. When you register on the AfriPics website you will be asked to provide information relevant to knowing who the AfriPics users are.   This information may include: your name; e-mail address; company name; location and telephone number.  The required fields are indicated on the registration form.  You may opt not to provide the required information, this will, however limit the functionality available to you on the Website.
By providing us with this information, you consent to AfriPics using this information as outlined in this agreement, which should be read in conjunction with the terms and conditions applicable to the use of any image from the AfriPics website.  AfriPics shall be entitled to share this information with its associates as may be required from time to time to provide the services offered by AfriPics.
www.afripics.com uses traffic analysis software collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. When using the AfriPics website, certain information may be collected automatically, such as the website that referred you to AfriPics, your IP address, browser type, navigational information, such as which pages you view and the links you click while using our site.  This information is used to analyze our user and customer interests and helps us improve our website.   ”Cookies” may be used to save your preferences when on the website. You are free to set your browser preferences to block or refuse cookies, and or notify you before they are placed. The cookie does not contain any personal details.  We will not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes.
Please note that whilst we may place links on the AfriPics website to which we believe may be of interest to you, this does not imply an endorsement of these websites. AfriPics does not accept responsibility for the content contained in any linked site or privacy issues on other websites as they do not fall under our control.  Please consult their respective Privacy Policies.
Under the following circumstances AfriPics reserves the right to disclose your information: if it is required by law; in the event that it is reasonable and necessary to respond to claims;  to manage and protect the rights and interests of AfriPics, its suppliers, or the company in general.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
AfriPics reserves the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. In the event that the policy is updated, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy.
How we Work
About us
FAQ
Support Local
Contribute
Submission Guidelines
Legal
Terms and Conditions
